

Profile

A third year Interactive Art and Technology student strives to create and improve visual branding and digital experience through human-centred designs. My core competencies are graphics design, sketching, and visualizing content to best serve my users and their needs.

Skills

Design	Process	Tools
Sketching	Research	Photoshop
Illustration	Ideation	Illustator
Visual Branding	Wireframing	InDesign
Interface Design	Prototyping	Figma
Interaction Design	Testing	XD

Experience

Graphic Designer

Volunteer - SFU LYFE

September 2021 -Present

Illustrator

Freelance - Bonheur

November 2020 -October 2021

Orientation Leader

Volunteer - Fraser International College

September 2021

- Working in a marketing team of 5 members including VP of Marketing and social media coordinators.
- Designing graphics for social media posts and stories based on the branding guideline by using Photoshop, Illustator and Figma, which increases followers on Instagram.
- Worked as a freelancer for a online clothes shop.
- Communicated with the stakeholder to create visualization for social media posts based on the branding color.
- Created illustration and story highlights for Instagram by using vector on Figma and drawing on Procreate.
- Supported a group of 20 new college students to adapt to the new academic environment by organizing team-building activities to connect them together.
- Operated a campus tour to for the new students which helped them know where to find academic resources or support.

Education

Bachelor of Arts, Interactive Arts and Technology Publishing Minor

Simon Fraser University

January 2021 - Present

Communication, Art and Technology

Fraser International College

Septermber 2019 - December 2020